(whimsical music)
(bright upbeat music)
♪ I come home in the mornin' light ♪
♪ My mother says, "When you
gonna live your life right?" ♪
♪ Oh, Momma dear, we're
not the fortunate ones ♪
♪ And girls, they wanna have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls just wanna have fun ♪
(bright upbeat music)
♪ The phone rings in the
middle of the night ♪
♪ My father yells, "What you
gonna do with your life?" ♪
♪ Oh, Daddy dear, you know
you're still number one ♪
♪ But girls, they wanna have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls just wanna have ♪
♪ That's all they really want ♪
♪ Some fun ♪
♪ When the workin' day is done ♪
♪ Oh, girls, they wanna have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls just wanna have ♪
♪ Fun ♪
♪ Girls, they want ♪
♪ Wanna have fun ♪
♪ Girls wanna have ♪
(bouncy upbeat music)
♪ Some boys take a beautiful girl ♪
♪ And hide her away from
the rest o' the world ♪
♪ I wanna be the one to walk in the sun ♪
♪ Oh, girls, they wanna have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls just wanna have ♪
♪ That's all they really want ♪
♪ Is some fun ♪
♪ When the workin' day is done ♪
♪ Oh, girls, they wanna have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls just wanna have ♪
♪ Fun ♪
♪ Girls, they want ♪
♪ Wanna have fun ♪
♪ Girls wanna have ♪
♪ They just wanna ♪
♪ Girls ♪
♪ They just wanna, oh, girls ♪
♪ Girls just wanna have fun ♪
♪ Just wanna, they just wanna ♪
♪ They just wanna ♪
♪ Girls ♪
♪ They just wanna, oh, girls ♪
♪ Girls just wanna have fun ♪
♪ When the workin' ♪
♪ When the workin' day is done ♪
♪ Oh, when the workin' day is done ♪
♪ Oh, girls ♪
♪ Girls just wanna have fun, everybody ♪
♪ Huh, huh ♪
♪ They just wanna ♪
♪ Girls ♪
♪ They just wanna, oh, girls ♪
♪ Girls just wanna have fun ♪
♪ Just wanna, they just wanna ♪
♪ They just wanna ♪
♪ Girls ♪
♪ They just wanna, oh, girls ♪
♪ Girls just wanna have fun ♪
♪ When the workin' ♪
♪ When the workin' day is done ♪
♪ Oh, when the workin' day is done ♪
♪ Oh, girls ♪
♪ Girls just wanna have fun, everybody ♪
♪ Huh, huh ♪
♪ They just wanna ♪
♪ They just wanna, hey ♪
♪ Girls ♪
♪ They just wanna ♪
♪ They just wanna, oh, girls ♪
♪ Girls just wanna have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls just wanna have fun ♪
♪ They just wanna ♪
♪ When the workin' ♪
♪ When the ♪